Guide to the Grover C. Sherlin Washington Academy of Sciences (Washington, D.C.) records, 1898-2002 MS2210
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Joint Board on Science Education records, 1950-2000; Series 6
  - Records, 1959-1997; Series 6 Subseries 1
    - National Engineers Week magazine, 1973-1974; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - National Space Foundation suggestions for preparation of proposals, 1965; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - New Seal draft, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Office of Administrative services, equipment requisitions, 1981; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Physics, 1969; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Procedures, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Program notes and correspondence, 1962-1963; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Project ideas, 1971-1972; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Publications directory, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Questionnaires for AIEE members, 1962; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Records, circa 1955-circa 1965; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Records, 1961-1964; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Records, 1964-1965; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Records, 1983-1984; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Records, 1987-1988; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Reporter newsletter, 1970; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Responses to mailing from Finance Committee chairman, 1967-1969; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Responses to mailing from Finance Committee chairman, 1967-1969; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Science and Engineering records, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Speaker's bureau, 1970-1972; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Stationery, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Summary Report to National Science Foundation, 1962-1964; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Summer Science and Engineering Apprencice Program, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Teacher recognition, 1971; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Teacher recognition, 1971-1972; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Teacher recognition, 1972; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Topic list, 1972; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Toward a Richer Future pamphlet, undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Naval Propellant Plant correspondence, 1963; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Science fairs, 1970-1997; Series 6 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains records of the Montgomery Area Science Fair, the International Science and Engineering Fair, and other science fair records.
    - Application for membership Prince George's Science Fair Association, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 1970; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - International Science and Engineering Fair, 1985; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - International Science and Engineering Fair, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - International Science and Engineering Fair, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous records, circa 1980-circa 1987; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Montgomery Area Science Fair, 1979-1985; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Montgomery Area Science Fair, 1980-1985; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Montgomery Area Science Fair, 1980-1985; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Montgomery Area Science Fair, 1980-1985; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery Area Science Fair, 1982; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Montgomery Area Science Fair, 1983-1985; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery Area Science Fair, 1983-1988; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Montgomery Area Science Fair Association pamphlet, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Programs and publications, 1966-1968; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Registration and judging, 1985-1997; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Reports and correspondence, 1964-1966; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "Science Education Law Poses Problems for NSF", 1984; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Directories, 1955-1992; Series 6 Subseries 3
    This subseries contains contact information directories of the Joint Board on Science Education.
    - Archdiocese of Washington Annual Report of Schools, 1961-1962; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Contacts corrections, 1971; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Department of Commerce Business Services Directory, undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare Telephone directory, 1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Diamond Ordinance Fuze Laboratories telephone directory, 1955-1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Directories, 1959-1960; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Directories, 1959-1961; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Directories, 1962-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Directories, 1963-1965; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Directories, 1965-1968; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Directories, 1968-1970; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Directories, 1970-1972; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Directories, 1975-1976; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Directories, 1978-1979; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Directories, circa 1980; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Directories, 1984-1986; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Directories, 1987-1988; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Directories, 1988-1989; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Directories, 1989-1990; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Directories, 1991-1992; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Directory planning notebook, 1986; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Directory records, 1972; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Goddard Space Flight Center directory, 1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Maryland School Officials directory, 1957-1958; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous directories and registration lists, 1962-1963; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - National Science Teachers Association Membership directory, 1957; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - NOL telephone directory, 1955-1956; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - School contacts from 1980-1982 directory, Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Science Teachers of Prince George's County, 1958-1959; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - University of Maryland telephone directory, 1956-1957; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce telelphone directory, 1962; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Naval Research Laboratory telephone directory, 1957-1962; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Who's Who Among American High School Students, 1980-1981; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Membership and Fellowship records, 1955-1999; Series 7
  This series contains membership and fellowship records of the Washington Academy of Sciences.
  Arranged into two subseries: Membership records and Fellowship records.
  - Membership records, 1979-1998; Series 7 Subseries 1
    Arranged alphabetically, then chronologically.
    This subseries includes membership and dues records.
    - Dues records, 1979; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Dues records, 1980; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Dues records, 1982; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Dues records, 1983; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Dues records, 1985; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Dues records, 1986; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Dues records, 1986; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Dues records, 1987; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Dues records, 1988; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Dues records, 1993; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Membership Directory, 1985-1993; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Membership records, 1977; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Membership records, 1981; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Membership records, 1985; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Membership records, 1986; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Membership records, 1987; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Membership records, 1988; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Membership records, 1990; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Membership records, 1998; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Fellowship records, 1955-1999; Series 7 Subseries 2
    This subseries includes fellows' publications and nomination records.
    - Fellows certificate, undated; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Fellows' publications, 1955-1957; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Fellows' publications, 1957-1959; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Fellows' publications, 1959-1960; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      General
      Titles in this folder: - Radio Corporation of America High-Fidelity Amplifier Circuits - The Audio Recovery Directory - GE Techni-talk vol. 12, no. 4 - House of Delegates No. 65 - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory of the University of California - Nuclear Electric Monopole Transitions by Michael Nessin
    - Fellows' publications, 1961; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Titles in this folder: - Semiannual Report Biology and Medicine UC Berkeley Lawrence Radiation Laboratory - AEC Computing and Applied Mathematics Center: The Singularities of the Riemann Function by: Donald Ludwig - Electrodes for Recording Primary Bioelectrical Signals by: M. Sosnow and E. Ross; U.S. Air Force Aeronautical Systems Division
    - Fellows' publications, 1962; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Titles in this folder: - U.S. Army Research Office (Durham): A Historical Summary - Effects of the Atmosphere on Radio Astronomical Signs by: Robert Fleischer, Masakazu Oshima, Terry P. Roark, Ronald M. Straka, and Marvin DeJong; United States Air Force - Development of a Rocketsonde Instrument Package for High Altitute Meteorological Sounding by: J.H. Stoudenmire, R.T. McCoy, and D.R. Greene; United States Air Force - University of California Ernest O. Lawrence Radiation Laboratory Bio-Organic Chemistry Quarterly Report
    - Fellows' publications, 1962; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Titles in this folder: - The Natural Rubber Producers' Research Association Publication No. 439 by: M.B. Evans and J.F. Smith - The George WAshingotn University Federalist Spring 1962 - E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Co. Mathematics and Computers, Fortran Codes for Computing Reactor Flux Shapes in One Dimension by: W.V. Baxter - University of California Ernest O. Lawrence Radiation Laboratory, The Effects of Ion Hydration in Solvent Extraction and Ion Exchange - Jet Propulsion Laboratory, CIT, Performance Calculations for Monopropellant Hydrazine and Monopropellant Hydrazine--Hydrazine Nitrate Mixtures by: Donald H. Lee -
    - Fellows' publications, 1962; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Titles in this folder: - General Electric, Alum Production Studies by: G. Jansen, Jr. - General Electric, Coolant Chemistry Instrumentation Studies for Pressurized Water Reactors: Wet Chemical Analysis by: T.F. Demmitt - General Electric, Interim Report, Ultrasonic Testing of Zircaloy Sheath Tubing for Fuel Elements by: C.E. Fitch, H.E. May, and V.E. Kale - The A&M College of Texas Department of Oceanography and Meteorology, Time Changes in a Temperate Latitude Cloud and Weather System as Revealed by Meteorological Satellite Data by: Darryl Randerson - Army Gas-Cooled Reactor Systems Program, Pecan II A Cycle Analysis Code for Gas Turbine, Nuclear or Conventional Power Plants, Modfied for Problems Involving Intercooled Compressors
    - Fellows' publications, 1962; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Titles in this folder: - Volumes 1-3: Kaman Nuclear, Two-Point Variability of Wind by: C. Eugene Buell
    - Fellows' publications, 1962; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Titles in this folder: - General Electric, Nuclear Materials & Propulsion Operation by: J.E. MacDonald, J.T. Martin, J.P. Yalch - United States Air Force, Effective Area of Satellite-Borne Antennas for Radio Astronomy by: Sheldon S. Sandler - Air Force Office of Scientific Research, Optimum Soft Landing Trajectories Part 2: Numerical Results by: Lawrence J. Berman - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory of the Univeristy of California, Temperature-Composition Diagrams of Pseudo-Binary Systems Containing Plutonium (III) Halides
    - Fellows' publications, 1962; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Titles in this folder: - CIT Jet Propulsion Laboratory, Space Programs Summary No. 37-18, Volume IV, Supporting Research and Advanced Development - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, A Study of the Kinetics of Uranyl Sulfate Exchange with a Strong Base Anion Resin by: J.S. Watson - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, The Rate of Reaction of Hydrogen From Hydrogen-Helium Streams with Fixed Beds of Copper Oxide by: C.D. Scott
    - Fellows' publications, 1962; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Titles in this folder: - Department of Civil Engineering Auburn Research Foundation - various Journal of Applied Physics articles - Melting Pressure Equation for the Hydrogens by: R.D. Goodwin - Rate of Graphitization of Carbon by: S. Mizushima - Further Studies of Electron Spin Reasonance in Chars, Carbons, and Graphites by: S. Mrozowski - Trapped Radicals in Organic Deposits by: R. Mangiaracina and S. Mrozowski - Memoirs of the American Mathematical Society, On the Ideal Structure of Operator Algebras by: Reese T. Prosser - Advanced Materials Technology, Carborundum - U.S. Naval Civil Engineering Laboratory, Distilling Sea Water with Diesel Generator Wast Heat - United States Air Force, The Radiative Decay of Metastable Argon Atoms in a Low-Density Argon Plasma Stream by: L.E. Brewer and W.K. McGregor - The A&M College of Texas Department of Oceanography and Meteorology, Vertical Motion Calculations and Satellite Cloud Observations Over the Western and Central United States
    - Fellows' publications, 1963; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Titles in this folder include: - Ames Laboratory Research and Development Report, A Fortran Program for Determinig the Thermal Diffusivity of Finite Length Samples by: Paul D. Maycock - United States Atomic Energy Commission, Earthquakes in the USSR book 2 - Boeing Scientific Research Laboratories, The Effects of Hall Currents and Asymmetric Inlet Conditions in Inviscid Constant Area Channel Flows by: Gordon C. Oates - GE Space Sciences Laboratory, Theory of Hypersonic Laminar Stagnation Region Heat Transfer in Dissociating Gases, by: S.M. Scala and L.M. Gilbert - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, The Principle of Design of Magnetic Momentum Slits by: E.L. Chu and J. Ballam
    - Fellows' publications, 1963-1964; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Titles in this folder include: - United States Atomic Energy Commission, Development of Depleted-Uranium Catalysts for Destruction of Air Pollutants in Automobile Exhaust - Operational Applications Laboratory, US Air Force, Acquisition of a Probabilistic Discrimination Between Subsequent Alternative Events by: Donald b. Cameron - ACHEMA, European Convention of Chemical Engineering, Frankfurt - Asarco Digest Number 3
    - Fellows Nominees, 1966-1967; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1967-1969; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1970-1974; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1981-1983; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1985; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1985; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1985; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1985; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1986; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1987; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1988; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1989; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1990; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1992; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1995; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1996; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1997; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Fellows Nominees, 1999; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Publications, 1899-2001; Series 8
  This series contains publications of the Washington Academy of Sciences, including Journal and Proceedings.
  Arranged alphabetically by publication, then chronologically.
  - Journal, vol. 1, 1911; Series 8 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 2, 1912; Series 8 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 3, 1913; Series 8 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 4, 1917; Series 8 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 5, 1915; Series 8 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 6, 1916; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 7 No.1-10, 1917; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 7 No.11-21, 1917; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 8 No. 1, 2, 9, 16-21, 1918; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 9 No. 1-10, 1919; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 9 No. 11-21, 1919; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 10, 1920; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 11 No. 1-10, 1921; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 11 No. 11-21, 1921; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 13, 1923; Series 8 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 14 No. 1-11, 1924; Series 8 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 14 No. 12-21, 1924; Series 8 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 15, 1925; Series 8 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 16, 1926; Series 8 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 17, 1927; Series 8 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 18, 1928; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 19, 1929; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 20 No. 1-11, 1930; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 20 No. 12-21, 1930; Series 8 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 21 No. 1-11, 1931; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 21 No. 12-21, 1931; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 22 No. 1-11, 1932; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 22 No. 12-21, 1932; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 23 No. 1-6, 1933; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 23 No. 7-12, 1933; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Journal, vol. 24 No. 1-6, 1934; Series 8 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Journal, vol. 24 No. 7-12, 1934; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 25 No. 1-6, 1935; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 25 No. 7-12, 1935; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 26, 1936; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 27 No. 1-6, 1937; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 27 No. 7-12, 1937; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 28 No. 1-6, 1938; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 28 No. 7-12, 1938; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 29 No. 1-6, 1939; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 29 No. 7-12, 1939; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 30 No. 1-6, 1940; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Journal, vol. 30 No. 7-12, 1940; Series 8 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 31 No. 1-6, 1941; Series 8 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 31 No. 7-12, 1941; Series 8 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 32 No. 1-6, 1942; Series 8 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 32 No. 7-12, 1942; Series 8 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 33, 1943; Series 8 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Journal, vol. 50, 1960; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 51, 1961; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 52, 1962; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 53, 1963; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 54, 1964; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 55, 1965; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Journal, vol. 56, 1966; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Journal, vol. 57, 1967; Series 8 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Journal, vol. 58, 1968; Series 8 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 59, 1969; Series 8 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 60, 1970; Series 8 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 61, 1971; Series 8 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 62, 1972; Series 8 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 63, 1973; Series 8 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Journal, vol. 64, 1974; Series 8 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Journal, vol. 65, 1975; Series 8 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 66, 1976; Series 8 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 67, 1977; Series 8 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 68, 1978; Series 8 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 69, 1979; Series 8 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 70, 1980; Series 8 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Journal, vol. 71, 1981; Series 8 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Journal, vol. 72, 1982; Series 8 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Journal, vol. 73, 1983; Series 8 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 74, 1984; Series 8 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 75, 1985; Series 8 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 76, 1986; Series 8 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 77, 1987; Series 8 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 80, 1990; Series 8 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Journal, vol. 81, 1991; Series 8 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Journal, vol. 82, 1992; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Journal, vol. 83, 1993; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Journal, vol. 84, 1996; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Journal, vol. 85, 1998; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Journal, vol. 86, 2000; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Journal, vol. 87, 2001; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Journal Records, 1969; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Journal Records, 1977; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Journal Records, 1980-1981; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Journal Records, 1982-1983; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Journal Records, 1985-1986; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Journal Records, 1987-1988; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Journal Records, 1989-1990; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Journal Records, 1991-1993; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Journal Records, 1995; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Journal Records, 1996; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Journal Records, 1997-1998; Series 8 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Proceedings, vol. 1, 1899; Series 8 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, vol. 2, 1900; Series 8 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings, vol. 3, 1901; Series 8 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, vol. 4, 1902; Series 8 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, vol. 5, 1903; Series 8 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings, vol. 6, 1904; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, vol. 7, 1905; Series 8 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings, vol. 8, 1906; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, vol. 9, 1907; Series 8 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings, vol. 10, 1908; Series 8 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings, vol. 11, 1909; Series 8 (Box 54, Folder 2)